<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>1A Full Broadcasts</title><link>http://larskiesow.de/test.atom</link><description>1A is a new show for a changing America. Every day, host Joshua Johnson convenes a conversation about the most important issues of our time. The show takes a deep and unflinching look at America, bringing context and insight to stories unfolding across the country and the world. With a name inspired by the First Amendment, 1A explores important issues such as policy, politics, technology, and what connects us across the fissures that divide the country. The program also delves into pop culture, sports, and humor. 1A's goal is to act as a national mirror-taking time to help America look at itself and to ask what it wants to be. The conversation isn't just on air. 1A invites you to join in. We'll regularly post questions and requests for feedback on this page. And you can talk to us on Twitter, Facebook, or by texting 1A to 63735. 1A is produced by WAMU 88.5, and distributed by NPR.</description><atom:link href="http://larskiesow.de/test.atom" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://the1a.org/wp-content/themes/wamu-show/img/logos/1a_logo_sm_128.svg</url><title>1A Full Broadcasts</title><link>http://larskiesow.de/test.atom</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 20:09:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Friday News Roundup - International</title><description>Why the U.S. deployed thousands of troops to Poland. How Donald Trump's cabinet nominees might affect America's international ties. And why the Norwegians have had enough of F.M. radio. A panel of journalists joins Joshua Johnson for analysis of the week's top international news stories.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170113.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Friday News Roundup - Domestic</title><description>Dodgy dossiers, a heartfelt farewell and the latest on the effort to repeal Obamacare. It's been a very busy start to the New Year and Joshua Johnson will break much of it down - on this week's Friday News Round Up. A panel of journalists joins Joshua for analysis of the week's top national news stories.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170113.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Tense And Totally Overshadowed: The Cabinet Confirmation Hearings</title><description>What's next in an already tense week for the President-elect's cabinet appointees?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170112.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Decoding Donald Trump's Testy News Conference</title><description>It was some spectacle. At his first news conference as president-elect, Donald Trump tossed aside accusations of sleazy behavior, he bulldozed his way through a wall of reporter's questions and announced who he had picked to run his company.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170112.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>What Works In The Fight Against Homelessness?</title><description>Some states and cities, including Utah, Massachusetts and Denver have significantly reduced the number of homeless people through an innovative strategy called "Housing First." In this hour, we'll talk to governors, former mayors, experts, and formerly homeless people about what works and why.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170111.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes, He Tried? Understanding Obama's Legacy</title><description>President Obama was all about hope. He leaves warning against fear. After his farewell address in Chicago, how will history judge his presidency? At 55 percent his job approval is equivalent to Ronald Reagan's at the same point, and ahead of Bill Clinton's. It is more than 20 points higher than George W. Bush's. But Donald Trump has promised to repeal the Affordable Care Act, possibly pull the U.S. out of the Paris agreement on climate change and tear up the U.S.-Iran nuclear deal. Each would undo some of President Obama's most visible achievements. What does he leave behind?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170111.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Evaluating the US Military in 2017</title><description>What is the state of the US military? Former Secretary of Defense Chuck Hagel weighs in.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170110.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Obamacare On Life Support</title><description>What would happen to you tomorrow if the Affordable Care Act was repealed today?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170110.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Politically Speaking: Talking To Each Other With Civility</title><description>Learning to live together after our nasty election: if a house divided against itself cannot stand, then America right now feels pretty shaky. Joshua Johnson asks how we get past the name-calling, and treat each other like human beings.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170109.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art of (Cyber)War</title><description>They say all is fair in love and war. But what if that war takes place behind a computer screen? We'll discuss what, exactly, constitutes as an act of war, and where cyberwarfare is headed in the future.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170109.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Friday News Roundup - International</title><description>Turkey starts the new year as it ended the old one - in turmoil. Why the manslaughter conviction of an Israeli soldier has become a lightning rod for both the Israelis and the Palestinians. And the U.K.'s Brexit ambassador unexpectedly quits - with some choice words for his political masters in London. A panel of journalists joins Joshua Johnson for analysis of the week's top international news stories.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170106.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Friday News Roundup - Domestic</title><description>Debate and analysis of the top news stories, including the fight to save or repeal the Affordable Care Act and President-elect Donald Trump's questioning of the "intelligence" from what will be his own intelligence agencies. And, why some are telling the Radio City Rockettes to "just shut up and dance." A panel of journalists joins Joshua Johnson for analysis of the week's top national news stories.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170106.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>The Politics Of Laughing</title><description>Who says politics is no laughing matter? The way we joke about our government and its leaders has evolved through the years.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170105.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Order In The Classroom: From Hall Monitors To Handcuffs</title><description>Are we criminalizing normal childhood behavior? A video posted on Twitter this week shows a female student being slammed to the ground by a school resource officer in Wake County, N.C. The footage has drawn renewed attention to the presence of police in schools and the treatment of kids at the hands of those officers.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170105.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Era of American Humanitarian Intervention Over?</title><description>Syria rests on the brink. South Sudan teeters on the edge of disaster. And all across the globe, fires rage and the threat of humanitarian crisis looms large. But how should the United States respond to these conflicts abroad?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170104.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Smart Technology: The Stalker In Your Pocket</title><description>What are your devices overhearing, and who else can listen?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170104.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>An Even More Perfect Union?</title><description>American democracy may be far from perfect, but is there another system that's better? We want to know how you would makeover the U.S. government.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170103.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Congress Is Back &amp; Watchdog Worries in 2017</title><description>Congress is back in session. What bills have bipartisan support? And why did House Republicans decide to gut Congress' independent watchdog?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170103-2.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump And Russia: Reset Or Retaliate?</title><description>Relations between the U.S. and Russia have gotten off to a rocky footing in 2017. With the Obama administration ejecting nearly three dozen Russian officials and imposing sanctions in retaliation for alleged election hacking. Is the new Commander-in-Chief looking for a Russian reset or other ways to retaliate?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170103-1.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>The 2017 Global Lookahead</title><description>The U.S.-Russia feud, the crisis in Syria, China's growing might, the rate of Brexit, the fate of the Paris climate accord — and an untested U.S. president forced to grapple with it all. We look at the big global issues of 2017.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170102-2.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>Some Real Talk On Fake News</title><description>Has fake news gotten out of control? How much can fabricated stories influence our ideas and even our politics?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a2170102-1.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 11:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>2017, You Have Our Attention</title><description>What will the biggest conversations of 2017 be?</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170102-2.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>What's 1A Anyway?</title><description>We're 1A, a new show from WAMU and NPR that celebrates free expression -- your free expression -- and the laws that protect it.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/17/01/a1170102-1.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item><item><title>How Math, Emotion And Naivete Helped OK Go Crack The Viral Code</title><description>OK Go's music videos are designed to dazzle. Their most recent, for the song "Upside Down and Inside Out," literally takes viewers to new heights with the use of parabolic flight to create weightlessness. That video earned the band and Trish Sie the Smithsonian Magazine 2016 American Ingenuity Award for Visual Arts. Joshua sits down with OK Go's lead singer Damian Kulash, bassist Tim Nordwind and video director and cinematographer Trish Sie, to discuss what drives them to push artistic boundaries in their work.</description><enclosure url="http://downloads.wamu.org/mp3/1a/16/12/a1161220.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 10:00:00 -0456</pubDate></item></channel></rss>